https://luda.ca/privacy/

Privacy Policy
Our Commitment to Your Privacy
At LUDA Foods, we share your concern about the way in which the information about you is used and shared, and we have outlined in this privacy notice the manner in which we collect, utilize, maintain, and disclose information which is obtained from users of this site, luda.ca.
Our Policy
This Policy relates only to our online information collection and use practices.
Collection of Information
LUDA Foods collects personal information which you provide to us through the use of our website. This information may include a person’s name, telephone number, address and email address. This information is utilized to respond to your questions and comments.
Like many websites we may use “cookies”, a software which identifies users when they revisit a website. These help us to track more effectively how our site is used and to identify features which may improve the site experience for our users.
Usage of Information
LUDA Foods will not share a user’s personal information with any third party or any other user without such user’s prior consent except under the conditions described below:
Communication from time to time via email to provide information about our website and its services;
Compliance with any applicable law, regulation, or legal action.
You may choose not to provide certain information to us, but it may prevent you from using all of the features of our website. You may also indicate at any time your choice not to receive email or other communications from us.
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy you can contact us either via the contact us form on this website, or at:
Or call us at : 514-695-3333 or 1 800 267-3333 (8 a.m. – 4 p.m. Eastern Time, Monday through Friday.)
